-What the hell? -Emergency preparedness drill.
- Quoi ? - Exercice d'état d'alerte.
-Oh, no. Come on. -Yeah, you know how it works.
- Non. - Tu sais comment ça marche.
Once a quarter, keep our readiness up.
Etre prêt une fois par trimestre.
Now, rise and shine, sleepy head. Half the town is probably dead.
Debout, Dormeur. Tout le monde est déjà mort.
LEONARD: l have to get a lock for my door.
Faut que je mette un verrou.
I think you'll like the drill tonight. I've tried to make it fun.
L'exercice va te plaire. Je l'ai rendu sympa.
Each of these cards contains a detailed scenario of a possible apocalyptic event.
Chaque carte expose le scénario d'un événement apocalyptique.
Everything from wildfires to a surprise invasion by Canada.
De feu de forêt à l'invasion surprise par le Canada.
Pick a catastrophe, any catastrophe.
Choisis n‘importe quelle catastrophe.
Sheldon, Canada is not going to invade California.
Sheldon, le Canada ne va pas envahir la Californie.
Yeah, really? You think those hippies in Washington and Oregon can stop them?
Les hippies de Washington et d'Oregon vont pouvoir les arrêter.
Alrighty. An 8.2 magnitude earthquake devastates Pasadena...
Génial. Un séisme de 8,2 dévaste Pasadena,
...reducing mighty edifices to dust, engulfing the city in flames...
les immeubles s'effondrent, les villes brûlent,
...the streets flow with blood and echo with the cries of the wounded.
les rues sont en sang, on entend les cris des blessés.
Oh, excellent choice. Now, put on your hard hat and safety vest.
Excellent choix. Enfile ton casque et ton gilet.
Oh, fun. I get to spend another night in front of our apartment...
Super. Une autre nuit dehors
...dressed like one of the Village People.
déguisé en Village People.
You make thatjoke every three months, I still don't get it. Leonard, wait.
Tu radotes. Je ne comprends pas ta blague.
-What are you doing? -I don't know. What am I doing?
- Que fais-tu ? - Je l‘ignore. Je fais quoi ?
Look around you, there's hypothetical broken glass everywhere.
Regarde autour de toi, il y a du verre brisé de partout.
Really? You're going to face Armageddon without your orthotics? Your choice.
Armageddon sans semelles orthopédiques ? A toi de voir.
-Uh-oh! Hypothetical aftershock. -Unh! Aah!
Une réplique.
And that's why we wear hard hats.
D'où l‘utilité du casque.
Check it out. Press release. From NASA.
Communiqué de presse dela NASA.
Crew members will include Commander Tom "Tombo" Johnson...
Le commandant Tom ”Tombo" Johnson,
...astronaut Mike "Supernova" Novacelik, and payload specialist Howard Wolowitz."
Mike ”Supernova" Novacelik et le manipulateur Howard Wolowitz."
This is going right into my synagogue's newsletter.
Je l'inclus dans le bulletin dela synagogue.
If you're going to be an astronaut, you need to pick a cool nickname.
Quitte à être astronaute, choisis un surnom cool.
I don't get to. The other guys have to give it to me.
Ce sont les autres qui doivent le choisir.
Oh. lfl had one, it would be Brown Dynamite.
Le mien, ce serait Dynamite Marron.
Are you not listening to me? The other astronauts have to give you your nickname.
Tu m‘écoutes ? Les autres le choisissent.
Are you not looking at me? I am Brown Dynamite.
Tu me regardes ? Je suis Dynamite Marron.
Why do you put six sugars in your coffee?
Pourquoi tu mets six sucres ?
Because the cafeteria doesn't offer little packets of methamphetamine.
La cafétéria ne propose pas de méthamphétamine.
-Emergency drill night last night, huh? -Uh-huh.
Encore un exercice de nuit ?
-How'd you do? -l'll tell you exactly how he did.
- Alors ? - Je vais vous le dire.
"Readiness: Unsatisfactory. Follows direction: Barely.
”Résultat : laisse à désirer. Obéit aux ordres : a peine.
Attitude: A little too much.
Attitude : trop marquée.
Overall: Not only will he probably die in a fiery inferno...
En résumé : il mourrait dans un brasier,
...his incessant whining would most certainly spoil everyone else's day."
et ses jérémiades empireraient les choses pour tout le monde."
You know what, I'm so tired I can't even think straight. I'm going home.
Je suis vraiment trop crevé. Je rentre.
Can one of you give this nutbag a ride later?
Qui pourra raccompagner ce tordu ?
You can't go home. You have to take me to the dentist at 4:00.
Tu dois m‘emmener chez le dentiste a 16 h.
-Oh. Can't you take the bus to the dentist? -Of course I can.
- Tu ne peux pas prendre le bus ? - Si.
It's coming back under the effects of the anesthesia that's the problem.
Mais le probléme de l'anesthésie va se poser.
Two years ago, after a deep gum cleaning...
Il y a deux ans, après un détartrage,
...I thought I got on a bus but somehow wound up on a booze cruise to Mexico.
je me suis retrouvé dans une virée alcoolisée au Mexique.
-They put you under for a cleaning? -Yeah, they have to. I'm a biter.
- On t'anesthésie ? - Obligé. Je mords.
Okay, whatever. Sheldon, I'm exhausted. I'm not taking you to the dentist.
C‘est ça. Sheldon, je suis crevé. Je ne t‘emménerai pas.
Wrong, sir. Wrong. Under Section 37B of the Roommate Agreement...
Faux. D‘après le paragraphe 315 du Contrat du coloc,
...Miscellaneous Duties, you are obligated to take me to the dentist.
tu as obligation de m‘emmener chez le dentiste.
See? Here, after "providing a confirmation sniff on questionable dairy products."
Après ”sentir les produits laitiers douteux par précaution".
You know what? I am sick of the Roommate Agreement.
J'en ai marre de ce Contrat.
It's ridiculous, I'm your roommate, not your chauffeur.
Je suis ton coloc, pas ton chauffeur.
I had better things to do yesterday...
J‘avais mieux a faire hier
...than drive you to the good model train store in Garden Grove...
que de t'emmener au bon magasin de maquettes de train
...because the one in Pasadena has gotten too big for its britches.
parce qu'à celui de Pasadena, ils ont pris la grosse tête.
Well, it has. Ask anybody.
C‘est le cas. N‘importe qui te le dira.
I don't care. I'm done.
Rien a faire. J‘arrête.
Hold on. Are you saying that you want to invoke Clause 209?
Attends. Tu comptes invoquer Ia Clause 209 ?
I don't know what that is, but if it means I can go home and sleep, then yes.
J'ignore ce que c'est, mais si je peux rentrer dormir, oui.
Think carefully here. Clause 209 suspends our friendship...
Réfléchis bien. La clause 209 suspend notre amitié
...and strips the Roommate Agreement to its essentials.
et réduit le Contrat du coloc au minimum.
Our responsibilities toward each other would be rent...
Nos responsabilités se limiteraient au loyer
...utilities and a perfunctory chin jut of recognition as we pass in the hall.
et a un salut de la tête quand on se croise dans le couloir.
What's up?
Salut !
Where do I sign?
Je signe où ?
Right here. Use your finger.
La. Utilise ton doigt.
-There. Done. SHELDON: All right.
- C‘est fait. - Bien.
That's it. We are now no longer companions, boon or otherwise.
On n‘est plus compagnons, bon ou autre.
We are now merely acquaintances.
On est de simples connaissances.
To amend the words of Toy Story, you have not got afriend in me.
Pour citer Toy Story, je ne suis pas ton ami.
-l'm gonna go home and take a nap. -Yeah, well, tell it to someone who cares.
- Je vais faire une sieste. - J'en ai rien a faire.
I got pretty exciting NASA news today.
Super nouvelle dela NASA.
Next week, I fly to Houston for orientation and zero-gravity elimination drills.
Je vais faire des exercices d‘élimination en gravité zéro.
-What does that mean? -He's gonna learn to poop in space.
- Quoi ? - Faire caca dans l‘espace.
Open the pod bay doors, HAL.
HAL, ouvre la porte.
Maybe your nickname should be Brown Dynamite.
Ton surnom devrait être Dynamite Marron.
Hello, dear friends. And Dr. Hofstadter.
Bonjour, les amis. Et Dr Hofstadter.
What's up?
Salut !
My apologies.
Excusez-moi.
I would've been here sooner but the bus kept stopping for other people to get on it.
J'arrive en retard, car le bus s'arrêtait tous les 500 m.
I saved you a dumpling.
Je t'ai gardé une boulette.
Oh. Your concern for me is touching.
C‘est trés gentil.
It will serve you well when you take me to the dentist tomorrow.
Mange-Ia demain en m'emmenant chez le dentiste.
I'm sorry, Sheldon, I'm busy. I'm right in the middle of my addiction study.
Désolée, je suis prise. J'étudie la dépendance.
I've got a lab full of alcoholic monkeys, and tomorrow we switch them to O'Doul's.
J'ai un labo plein de singes bourrés, on les passe àla bière sans alcool.
You're my girlfriend and you're not going to cater to my every need?
Ma copine refuse de satisfaire tous mes besoins ?
Oh, where'd the magic go?
La magie a disparu.
Sheldon, that's not what girlfriends are for.
Une copine ne sert pas a ça.
Although, you don't use them for what they're for, so what do I know?
Tu ne t'en sers pas comme il faut, a quoi bon.
Howard doesn't make me do his shopping, take him to the dentist...
Howard ne m'envoie pas faire ses courses
-...or pick up his dry cleaning, right? -Absolutely. But when Ma's hips give out...
- ou chez le teinturier. - Quand maman sera grabataire,
...you're up, kid.
tu t‘y colleras.
Well, if Amy's too busy, it gives the rest of you an opportunity to make my life easier...
Si Amy est prise, vous pouvez me faciliter la vie
...thus assuring yourselves a footnote in my memoirs...
et vous aurez une note de bas de page dans mes mémoires
...tentatively entitled You're Welcome, Mankind.
provisoirement appelées De rien, humanité.
All right, then. Just shout when you hear the task you want to undertake.
Bon. Criez quand vous voulez vous charger d‘une tâche.
Uh, dentist.
Dentiste.
Okay, we can circle back to that one. Um....
On y reviendra.
Who wants to take me Wednesday morning to get new heels put on my dress shoes?
Qui veut m‘emmener acheter de nouvelles talonnettes ?
Anyone? Oh.
Personne ?
That one had hoot written all over it.
Je vous avais tendu une perche.
Allergist.
Allergologue.
Podiatrist.
Pédicure.
Supercuts?
Coiffeur ?
Okay, okay, here's a fun one.
En voilà un sympa.
Um, I need a new picture frame and l have a hankering for Swedish meatballs.
Il me faut un nouveau cadre photo, etj'ai envie de boulettes suédoises.
Who wants to spend the day with me at lkea?
Qui veut passer lajournée avec moi a Ikea ?
-Their meatballs are good. -What?
- Leurs boulettes sont bonnes. - Quoi ?
Nothing. Nothing.
Rien.
Hello, Stuart.
Bonjour, Stuart.
Oh, hey, Sheldon. Can I help you find something today?
Salut, Sheldon. Je peux t‘aider ?
No, l was just sitting at home...
Non, j‘étais chez moi
...thinking about how it might be nice to catch up with my ninth favorite person.
etje me demandais ce que ma 9e personne préférée devenait.
-Ninth? -You moved up one.
- 9e ? - T'es monté d‘une place.
My pen pal in Somalia was kidnapped by pirates.
Des pirates ont kidnappé mon correspondant somalien.
So, uh, how are you?
Comment ça va ?
...and blamed me in the note.
et m‘a accusé.
Great, great.
Super.
So, what's new with your family? How's your mother? Is she alive?
Ta famille va bien ? Ta mère est en vie ?
Yeah.
Oui.
-Your father. Alive? -Yes.
- Et ton pére ? -Oui.
-How about your grandparents, they alive? -No.
- Et tes grands—parents ? - Non.
Oh, I'm so sorry for your loss.
Toutes mes condoléances.
On a cheerier note, I have a teeth-cleaning appointment this afternoon.
Pour te remonter le moral, le dentiste me fait un détartrage.
What do you say you take me over there, buddy boy?
Ça te dit de m‘y emmener, mon pote ?
Sorry, you want me to take you to the dentist?
T‘emmener chez le dentiste ?
Yes. And, now, I can't make any promises...
Oui. Je ne te promets rien,
...but that's the sort of thing that gets a fella on the list for the number eight friend slot.
mais ça pourrait te faire gagner une place.
Sheldon, I'm working. I can't take you to the dentist.
Sheldon,je bosse. Je ne peux pas.
Also, and I can't stress this enough, I don't want to take you to the dentist.
Sans oublier que je ne veux pas.
Can't help a friend out in a time of need, huh?
Tu refuses d‘aider un ami dans le besoin ?
I see where your therapist was coming from.
Je comprends ton psy.
You can't do Buzz. Buzz is taken.
Impossible. Buzz est déjà pris.
Buzz Lightyear is not real.
Buzz l'Eclair n'existe pas.
No, that's not what I'm talking about.
Ce n‘est pas ça.
Well, are you talking about when he thought he was real?
Tu parles de quand il croyait être vrai ?
Okay, um, oh, how about Crash? Howard "Crash" Wolowitz.
Et Crash ? Howard ”Crash" Wolowitz.
Terrific. The astronauts would love hurtling through space with a guy named Crash.
Génial. Ils vont adorer aller dans l'espace avec Crash.
All right, uh, how about--? Oh, how about Rocket Man?
Bon, et… Fusée ?
That's not bad. Howard "Rocket Man" Wolowitz.
C‘est pas mal. Howard ”Fusée" Wolowitz.
It's great, but I told you, I don't get to pick my nickname.
Oui, maisje ne peux pas le choisir.
It has to come from the other astronauts.
Ce sont les autres.
Maybe there's a way to get them to come up with it.
Tu peux peut-être les influencer.
Like how?
Comment ?
Once I tried carrying around a Duncan yo-yo...
Une fois, j‘avais un yo-yo,
...hoping the other kids would start calling me Duncan.
en espérant paraitre cool auprès des autres.
-Did it work? -No, they ended up calling me Sock Mouth...
- Alors ? - Ils m‘ont surnommé tête à claques,
...because they took away my yo-yo and stuffed their socks in my mouth.
pris mon yo-yo et fait bouffer leurs chaussettes.
Okay. Uh, what if we make "Rocket Man" your ringtone...
Et si ta sonnerie de portable était “Rocket Man“, ”la fusée".
...and the next time you talk to those guys, I'll call you and they'll hear it.
Je t'appellerai quand tu les verras, et ils l‘entendront.
That's not a terrible plan.
C‘est pas une mauvaise idée.
They don't call me Brown Dynamite for nothing.
Je ne suis pas Dynamite Marron pour rien.
-What's up?
- Salut.
You ever make it to the dentist?
T'es allé chez le dentiste ?
Not necessary. I found a service that'll send a van to your house for a teeth cleaning.
Inutile. On va venir me chercher en camionnette.
Mostly they cater to dogs...
Un livreur de nourriture pour chiens,
...but the fellow on the phone seemed to have an open mind.
mais le type semblait ouvert d‘esprit.
All right, Sheldon, if you need me to take you to the dentist, I will take you.
Si tu veux que je t‘y emmène, c‘est d‘accord.
Are you suggesting that you've come to your senses...
Tu suggéres que tu as repris tes esprits
...and wish to reestablish the benefits that stem from the Roommate Agreement?
et que tu veux rétablir les avantages issus du Contrat du coloc ?
Absolutely. If you admit you're a 30-year-old man incapable of functioning on his own.
Si tu reconnais être un type de 30 ans incapable d‘être indépendant.
I will admit nothing of the sort. And now, if you'll excuse me...
Jamais dela vie. Veuillez m'excuser,
...l have to call my dentist and see if I can get my hair shampooed and nails clipped.
j‘appelle mon dentiste pour voir s'il peut me faire les ongles.
-Oh, good, your power's out too. -Why is that good?
- Tant mieux, c‘est général. - Pourquoi ?
Last month, I sent the electric company a Starbucks gift card...
J'ai envoyé une carte cadeau a la société d‘électricité
...an apology note and a few snapshots of me in a bra.
et un mot d'excuse avec des photos de moi en soutif.
What happened to all your glow-in-the-dark emergency exit stuff painted on the floor?
Où sont tes signes phosphorescents peints au sol ?
Oh, that was wildly carcinogenic.
C‘était cancérigéne au possible.
Anyway, too bad you're no longer entitled to the full benefits of my friendship...
Dommage que tu n'aies plus droit aux avantages de mon amitié,
...because I happen to be extremely prepared for such an emergency.
carje suis trés préparé pour ce genre d'urgence.
Please try not to see anything by this light.
Regarde tout sauf cette lumière.
It's not for you.
Tu n‘y as pas droit.
It's a blackout, I'm sure the power will be back soon.
C‘est un black-out, ils vont remettre le courant.
And I'm sure some fool in the Donner Party said the snow would stop any day now.
Un idiot de l'expédition Donner a du dire que la neige s'arrêterait.
I like to think they ate him first.
Ils l‘ont sûrement mangé en premier.
I've got candles in my apartment.
J'ai des bougies chez moi.
Candles? During a blackout? Are you mad? That's a fire hazard.
Des bougies ? C‘est un risque d‘incendie.
No, Pasadena Water and Power recommends the far safer glow stick.
Non, les autorités recommandent les tubes fluo.
You call that a glow stick?
Ça, c‘est un tube fluo ?
That is a glow stick.
Non, ça, c‘est un tube fluo.
Come on, let's go.
Allons-y.
Before you go, consider this:
Avant de partir, médite là:—dessus :
Not only do I have a deep-cycle marine battery power source more than capable...
j'ai non seulement une batterie marine capable
...of running our entertainment system, I also have all 61 episodes...
de faire marcher nos appareils, j'ai aussi les 61 épisodes
...of the BBC series Red Dwarf.
dela série Red Dwarfde la BBC.
And Fiddle Faddle.
Et du pop—corn.
All yours if you're willing to reinstate the Roommate Agreement.
Tu peux les avoir, si tu signes le Contrat du coloc.
I've got wine at my place and some bubble wrap we could pop.
J'ai du vin chez moi et du papier bulle a éclater.
He'll be back. Wine and a girl in the dark, he's gonna be bored out of his mind.
Il reviendra. Du vin et une fille dans le noir, il trouvera ça rasoir.
To wine and bubble wrap.
Au vin et au papier bulle.
And to not having to watch Sheldon demonstrate his reverse osmosis machine...
Et pas àla machine d'osmose inverse de Sheldon
...that converts urine into drinking water.
qui transforme l‘urine en eau potable.
You know, in Girl Scouts, Tammie Dineesha said you could do that with panty hose.
D‘après Tammie Dineesha, ça marchait avec des collants.
Boy, was she wrong.
Elle se trompait.
Anyway, you wanna make out?
On se bécote ?
I thought because our relationship's in a beta test, you wanted to take things slow.
Notre relation est en bêta, tu ne veux pas prendre ton temps ?
Okay. Do you wanna make out slow?
On se bécote en prenant notre temps ?
I can go so slow it'll be like there's a snail in your mouth.
Oui, ce sera comme d‘avoir un escargot dans la bouche.
Lucky for you there's nothing else to do right now.
T'as dela chance qu'on soit coincés.
-Excuse me, Leonard. -Since when don't you knock?
- Excuse-moi. - Tu ne frappes plus ?
It's, like, the only good thing about you.
C‘est ta seule qualité.
Social niceties have been suspended. We're in a state of emergency.
Plus de politesse. On est en état d'urgence.
The world has descended into darkened turmoil...
Le monde sombre
...lawlessness and savagery are the order of the day.
dans l'anarchie et la sauvagerie.
-Fine, what is it? -l'm making s'mores.
- Qu'y a-t-il ? - Je fais griller des chamallows.
I wanted to alert you in case you smelled caramelizing marshmallows...
Je vous préviens, car si vous sentez l'odeur,
...and thought a nearby candy factory was on fire.
ce n‘est pas une usine de bonbons en feu.
-S'mores, huh? Good for you. -Yes.
- C‘est bien pour toi. - Oui.
Or good for us if you sign here and reinstate the full Roommate Agreement.
Ou bien pour nous, si tu signes notre Contrat du coloc.
No, thanks, I'm good.
Non, merci, ça ira.
Really? Oh.
Vraiment ?
Okay. In that case, I will have a s'more by myself.
Dans ce cas, je vais les manger tout seul.
And then I'm gonna have some more.
Jusqu'au dernier.
By myself.
Tout seul.
-But he's sad. -No, he's crazy.
- Il est triste. - Il est dingue.
Sometimes crazy looks like sad so it'll suck you back in.
Un dingue peut être triste pour te tromper.
I think he misses his little buddy.
Son pote lui manque.
Fine.
D‘accord.
But mark my words, this frustrating bogus teenage make out session is not over.
Mais ce simulacre de bécotage n‘est pas fini.
You said candles were dangerous.
Tu disais les bougies dangereuses.
This is a Bunsen burner.
C‘est un bec Bunsen.
I'm a scientist. I know what I'm doing.
Je suis scientifique. Je m‘y connais.
Oh, drat.
Fichtre !
Listen, Sheldon, this is stupid. I don't see why we can't be friends.
Tout ça est stupide. On peut être amis.
I'm willing to drive you and help you out with stuff...
Je veux bien te conduire et t'aider,
...I just don't want to because of some agreement.
mais pas a cause d'un contrat.
-What are you proposing? -That we go back to the way things were.
- Tu proposes quoi ? - On redevient comme avant.
But when I do something for you, you show a little appreciation.
Si je te rends service, pense a me remercier.
How would I do that?
Comment ça ?
-You say "thank you." -Every time?
- Dis "merci". - A chaque fois ?
It's not crazy.
Ce n‘est pas dingue.
Counter-proposal.
Contre-proposition.
We reinstate the full Roommate Agreement with the following addendum:
On réinstaure le Contrat avec cette annexe :
In the spirit of Mother's Day or Father's Day, once a year...
dans l'esprit de la fête des mères ou des pères, une fois par an,
...we set aside a day to celebrate all your contributions to my life...
on fixe un jour pour fêter toutes tes contributions à ma vie,
...both actual and imagined by you.
les vraies et les imaginaires.
We could call it Leonard's Day.
Ce serait le jour de Leonard.
I kind of like the sound of that.
Ça me plaît.
Of course you do. It's about you, like everything else.
Bien entendu. C‘est égoiste au possible.
Oh, thank goodness. I don't think I had it in me to make another glass of water.
Dieu merci. Je ne m'en sentais pas capable de refaire un verre d'eau.
So do I get breakfast in bed on Leonard's Day?
Petit—déj au lit le jour de Leonard ?
-No. -Can I sit in your spot?
- Non. - M'asseoir a ta place ?
-Could I control the thermostat?
- Contrôler le thermostat ?
-No. -Do I get a card?
- Non. - J‘aurai une carte ?
Of course you get a card.
Bien entendu.
It's Leonard's Day.
C‘est le jour de Leonard.
Hey, guys. The building manager said the reason the power went out...
La panne d‘électricité serait à cause
...is someone went into the basement and pulled the main breaker switch.
de quelqu'un qui a coupé le courant au sous-sol.
Really.
Vraiment.
Who do you think did that, Sheldon?
Oui ça peut bien être ?
Oh, I don't know.
Je ne sais pas.
But whoever that mystery man was, you should be eternally grateful...
Mais cet homme mystère devrait être remercié éternellement,
...for without him, there would be no Leonard's Day.
car sans lui, il n‘y aurait pas de jour de Leonard.
Leonard's Day?
Quoi ?
No pressure, just get him a crummy card, you're good.
Pas de pression, donne—lui une carte pourrie.
All right, test my ringtone.
Teste ma sonnerie.
-It really is a good song. -Yeah, there's a reason he's Sir Elton John.
- Super chanson. - C‘est pas Sir Elton John pour rien.
They don't make you a knight for writing "Wake Me Up Before You Go-Go."
On n‘est pas anobli avec ”Wake Me Up Before You Go-Go".
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Howard, are you coming down for breakfast?
Howard, tu descends petit-déjeuner ?
Ma, I told you, I have a video conference with NASA! I said don't bother me!
Maman, j'ai une vidéo-conférence avec la NASA !
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Ooh, listen to Mr. Big Shot Astronaut!
M. le Grand Astronaute parie !
Yes, please listen to Mr. Big Shot Astronaut!
Oui, écoute M. le Grand Astronaute !
Hey. Good morning.
Bonjour.
Hey, Howard. Thanks for getting up so early.
Salut. Merci de t'être levé si tôt.
No problem, Dr. Massimino.
Pas de problème, Dr Massimino.
The guys here call me Mass.
On me surnomme Mass.
Mass. That's a cool nickname, because force equals mass times acceleration.
Chouette surnom, force égale masse fois accélération.
Yeah. It's just short for Massimino.
C‘est le diminutif de Massimino.
Anyway, the plan for this morning is to go over the--
Bon. Le programme, c‘est de...
Sorry. My phone.
Désolé. Mon téléphone.
What is that? Is that "Rocket Man"?
C‘est quoi, “Rocket Man" ?
Yeah, it's my ringtone. Kind of my favorite song, "Rocket Man."
Oui, c‘est ma sonnerie. Ma chanson préférée “Rocket Man".
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Howard, your Froot Loops are getting soggy!
Howard, tes céréales sont molles !
Not now!
Pas maintenant !
-Who's that? -My mom. Sorry.
- C‘est qui ? - Ma mère, désolé.
No problem, Fruit Loops.
Pas de problème, Céréales Molles.
[English - us - SDH]
[French]